https://www.jazzguitar.be/blog/privacy-and-terms/

Skip to contentJGO HOMEJAZZ GUITAR LESSONSJAZZ GUITAR CHORDSGUITAR GEAReBOOKSFORUM
MenuJGO HOMEJAZZ GUITAR LESSONSJAZZ GUITAR CHORDSGUITAR GEAReBOOKSFORUM Privacy Policy and Terms of ServiceThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Jazz Guitar Online collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.jazzguitar.be website (“Site”).This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Jazz Guitar Online.Personal Identification InformationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and/or subscribe to the newsletter. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, and/or credit card information.Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-Personal Identification InformationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site.Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the internet service providers utilized, and other similar information.Browser CookiesOur Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes, registration, and sometimes to track information about them.User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How We Use Collected InformationJazz Guitar Online collects and uses Users’ personal information for the following purposes:To improve customer service – Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.To personalize user experience – We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To process transactions – We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.To send periodic emails – The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.How We Use Collected InformationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information, and data stored on our Site.Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.Sharing Your Personal InformationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.Terms and Conditions of UseBy accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.Use LicensePermission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Jazz Guitar Online’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: Modify or copy the materials. Use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial). Attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Jazz Guitar Online’s web site. Remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials.Transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Jazz Guitar Online at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.DisclaimerThe materials on Jazz Guitar Online’s web site are provided “as is”. Jazz Guitar Online makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights.Further, Jazz Guitar Online does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.LimitationsIn no event shall Jazz Guitar Online or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Jazz Guitar Online’s Internet site, even if Jazz Guitar Online or a Jazz Guitar Online authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.Revisions and ErrataThe materials appearing on Jazz Guitar Online’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Jazz Guitar Online does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Jazz Guitar Online may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Jazz Guitar Online does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.LinksJazz Guitar Online has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Jazz Guitar Online of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.Changes to These Terms and Privacy PolicyJazz Guitar Online has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modificationsYour Acceptance of These TermsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.About Jazz Guitar OnlineJazz Guitar Online was founded in 2003 by Dirk Laukens, who is the webmaster, publisher, and editor in charge.If you have inquiries about the website or our products, don’t hesitate to contact us.Jazz Guitar OnlineHolleweg 202950 KapellenBelgiumBE0886774394
>
Scroll to Top
